WEBSITE

orhanona.com

MOBILE

+972547686664

EMAIL

orhanona@gmail.com

OR OHANOUNA

I'm a passionate industrial designer with a right balance of aesthetic sensitivity & mechanical aptitude, a keen eye for detail, and ability to light up key software experiences through flagship hardware have allowed me to work on a broad range of exciting projects. I'm an adaptable person, working independently or as part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

based in Tel Aviv, Israel.

DESIGN & PRODUCT MANAGER FOTO MASTER LTD 2017 - PRESENT

Lead Designer for the in-house product development team in Foto Master, software and hardware company for the entertainment industry.

- Hands-on direction of all aspects of the product development cycle A-Z, while solving day to day problems.
- Work hand in hand with the software teams to deliver complete experiences.
- A key contributor to the design and success of the Mirror X Booth, modern photo booth. Sales were 300% more than first-year projections.
- Provided myself as a cross-functional role To help the company establish a sheet metal factory, based in CT, US.
- Developed multiple successful product lines in a wide variety of manufacturing technologies.

INDUSTRIAL DESIGNER FREELANCE DESIGN SERVICE 2016 – 2017

I provided design services for small and large clients. Diverse design disciplines include Industrial design, graphic design, exhibition design, and illustration.

- Worked closely with Design team to create Africa exhibition for Tel Aviv Museum and Natural Science exhibition for Bezalel Academy.
- Research design styles, materials and motifs to get a new viewpoint and produce design concepts for **Studio Cheha**.
- Designed and developed products through concept sketching, CAD, prototyping,
 3D renderings and videos for Studio Avidani

INDUSTRIAL DESIGNER ZØRE 2015 – 2016 Industrial designer at the new generation of gun storage start-up.

 Assisted Zøre team to launch in Indiegogo, a crowdfunding platform, the company raised 600,000USD.

EDUCATION

BEZALEL ACADEMY OF ART AND DE SIGN

B.Des in industrial design, graduated in 2016.

LANGUAGES

• SOLIDWORKS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

FABRICATION PROCESSES

ENGLISH HEBREW

• KEYSHOT

DYNAMIC PRODUCT ANIMATIONS

• INDESIGN

• SURFACE TREATMENTS

• SKETCHING & VISUALIZATION

ILLUSTRATORPHOTOSHOP

APPLICATION OF MATERIALS IN DESIGN

MS OFFICE

PROJECT MANAGEMENT